There are a lot of claims to fact check. Jason Puckett verifies
vice president mike Pence and Senator Kamala Harris took to the debate stage
Wednesday for the first and only vice presidential debate of this election.
Now right now we're breaking down one claim from each.
Here's Kamala Harris, do you know this administration
took the word science off the website
and then took the phrase climate change off the website.
This claim is true but needs context.
A study by the Environmental data and governance initiative tracked
government websites and found many agencies like the E.
P. A. Removed and changed parts of their websites during the trump admin.
These changes included the removal and quote
overhaul of climate change sections of sites including
the E P a
White house dot gov, Department of State and the Department of Energy.
Now it's true that mentions of climate change were removed from those sites,
but not all government websites have had the words removed
climate dot gov and clean net dot org.
Both government sites that have collections about
climate change still on their websites.
Right now, here's mike Pence.
When joe biden was vice president of the United States,
not 7.5 million people contracted the swine flu.
60 million americans contracted the swine flu.
This claim is true but needs context.
The CDC estimates for swine flu do show between
40 to 90 million estimated cases in the U.
S. Between 2009 and 2010.
So far, we have roughly 7.5 million confirmed Covid cases in the US,
it is important to point out that this is not the same
time period since Covid has not been around for a year yet.
Alright, so.